{
    "id": "45fae40c079d4dd5a540400f19b46c51",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The exam has been ………………………….",
            "description": "To put off is to postpone.",
            "answers": [
                "put out",
                "put off",
                "put up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I might ………………………… Susie in the evening.",
            "description": "To call on is to visit.",
            "answers": [
                "call on",
                "call up",
                "call in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Only a mentally strong person can ………………………….. the difficulties in life.",
            "description": "To get over is to overcome.",
            "answers": [
                "get off",
                "get over",
                "get on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "After trying for an hour or so, I …………………………..",
            "description": "To give up is to stop.",
            "answers": [
                "gave up",
                "gave off",
                "gave out"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He and his roommate ………………………….. really well.",
            "description": "To get along is to have a friendly relationship.",
            "answers": [
                "get off",
                "get along",
                "get over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My grandmother ……………………………… at the age of",
            "description": "To pass away is to die.",
            "answers": [
                "passed off",
                "passed on",
                "passed away"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have put a lot of effort ……………………… this project and I really want it to succeed.",
            "description": "To put effort into something is to make a lot of effort to do it. ",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "onto",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That table …………………………. a lot of space.",
            "description": "To take up space is to occupy space. ",
            "answers": [
                "takes on",
                "takes up",
                "takes in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. the document before signing it.",
            "description": "To go through a document is to read it carefully.",
            "answers": [
                "Go through",
                "Go over",
                "Go into"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It took them hours to ……………………………. the fire.",
            "description": "To put out fire is to extinguish it.",
            "answers": [
                "put out",
                "put in",
                "put up"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Sometimes adversity …………………………….. the best in people.",
            "description": "To bring out is to produce. ",
            "answers": [
                "brings out",
                "brings up",
                "brings off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………… an old friend of mine yesterday.",
            "description": "To run into somebody is to meet them unexpectedly. ",
            "answers": [
                "ran up",
                "ran into",
                "ran across"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}